Guide to the International Typographical Union Local 99 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- RECORD GROUP C: INTERNATIONAL TYPOGRAPHICAL UNION LOCAL 170 TACOMA, 1908-1978 (Box-folder 48/1-Box 57, 67/1)
  - SERIES IV: MINUTES - EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1913-1969 (Box-folder 51/3-52/37)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1916 (Box-folder 52/4)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1917 (Box-folder 52/5)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1918 (Box-folder 52/6)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1919 (Box-folder 52/7)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1920 (Box-folder 52/8)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1921 (Box-folder 52/9)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1922 (Box-folder 52/10)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1923 (Box-folder 52/11)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1924 (Box-folder 52/12)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1925 (Box-folder 52/13)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1926-1927 (Box-folder 52/14)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1927 (Box-folder 52/15)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1928 (Box-folder 52/16)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1929 (Box-folder 52/17)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1930 (Box-folder 52/18)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1931 (Box-folder 52/19)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1932-1933 (Box-folder 52/20)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1933-1934 (Box-folder 52/21)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1934 (Box-folder 52/22)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 52/23)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1936-1937 (Box-folder 52/24)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 52/25)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 52/26)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1939-1941 (Box-folder 52/27)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1941 (Box-folder 52/28)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1942 (Box-folder 52/29)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1943 (Box-folder 52/30)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1944 (Box-folder 52/31)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1945 (Box-folder 52/32)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 52/33)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1947 (Box-folder 52/34)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1948 (Box-folder 52/35)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1949 (Box-folder 52/36)
    - International Typographical Union Local 170 Minutes - Executive Committee, 1950 (Box-folder 52/37)
  - SERIES V: ARBITRATION PROCEEDINGS, 1914-1937, 1961 (Box-folder 52/38-52/47)
    - Election, arbitration, 1917-1920 (Box-folder 52/38)
    - Resolution, 1914 (Box-folder 52/39)
    - Miscellaneous Arbitration Materials, 1961 (Box-folder 52/40)
    - Republications, 1946 (Box-folder 52/41)
    - Proceedings, 1936 (Box-folder 52/42)
    - In Arbitration Proceedings, 1929-1934 (Box-folder 52/43)
    - Arbitration Proceedings, 1936 (Box-folder 52/44)
    - Arbitration Proceedings, 1937 (Box-folder 52/45)
    - Arbitration Proceedings, 1937 (Box-folder 52/46)
    - Arbitration Proceedings, 1937 (Box-folder 52/47)
  - SERIES VI: MEMBERSHIP MATERIALS, 1850-1974 (Box-folder 53/1-53/3,53/5-53/9)
    - Application for Membership, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 53/1)
    - Application for Membership, 1921-1923 (Box-folder 53/2)
    - Application for Membership, 1953 (Box-folder 53/3)
    - Record, 1934-1953 (Box-folder 53/5)
    - Union Meeting Attendance Record, 1953-1974 (Box-folder 53/6)
    - Registration Book Union Meeting, 1914-1933 (Box-folder 53/7)
    - Journal, 1850 (Box-folder 53/8)
    - Members of Tacoma Typographical Union #170 Record, 1885-1888 (Box-folder 53/9)
  - SERIES VII: FINANCIAL RECORDS - DUES, 1966 (Box-folder 53/4, 54/1)
    - Financial Record: Dues, 1966 (Box-folder 53/4)
    - Dues Account, Undated (Box-folder 54/1)
  - SERIES VII: FINANCIAL RECORDS - MONTHLY REPORTS, APPRENTICESHIP, AND PENSION PLAN MATERIALS, 1937-1974 (Box-folder 54/2-54/20)
    - Secretary's Monthly Itemized Report, 1937-1974 (Box-folder 54/2)
    - Monthly Summary Report, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 54/3)
    - Monthly Stamp Report, 1956-1961 (Box-folder 54/4)
    - Monthly Stamp Report, 1940-1956 (Box-folder 54/5)
    - International Typographical Union, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 54/6)
    - STU Info, 1964 (Box-folder 54/7)
    - Vets Forms, 1964 (Box-folder 54/8)
    - Unionism Tests, 1954 (Box-folder 54/9)
    - Letters, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 54/10)
    - Lessons in Printing, 1964 (Box-folder 54/11)
    - Forms, 1965 (Box-folder 54/12)
    - General Information, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 54/13)
    - Federal Reports, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 54/14)
    - Apprentice Committee Reports, 1966-1974 (Box-folder 54/15)
    - Apprentice Information, 1970 (Box-folder 54/16)
    - Applications for Apprenticeship, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 54/17)
    - Apprentice Committee Reports, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 54/18)
    - Joint Apprentice Committee, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 54/19)
    - Apprentice Regulations, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 54/20)
  - SERIES VIII: FINANCIAL RECORDS - TAXES, STRIKE BENEFITS, MUTUAL AID, STATEMENTS, REPORTS, 1928-1975 (Box-folder 55/1-56/59)
    - Financial Records and Communications, 1970 (Box-folder 55/1)
    - Organizational Amnesty, Strike Roll, 1959-1964 (Box-folder 55/2)
    - Budget Records and Proposal, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 55/3)
    - Committee Reports, c.1969 (Box-folder 55/4)
    - Washington State Apprenticeship Council, 1969 (Box-folder 55/5)
    - Proposed Amendment to Fraternal Pension Plan, c.1970 (Box-folder 55/6)
    - Report of Allied Delegates, Blank Arbitration Consent Forms, 1971 (Box-folder 55/7)
    - Audit Reports, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 55/8)
    - Audit Reports, 1959-1968 (Box-folder 55/9)
    - Johnson and Higgins' Annual Report to Trustees: STU-Employer Life and Disability Fund, 1971 (Box-folder 55/10)
    - Johnson and Higgins' Annual Report to Trustees: STU-Employer Life and Disability Fund, 1974 (Box-folder 55/11)
    - Johnson and Higgins' Actuarial Valuation Report, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 55/12)
    - Johnson and Higgins' Annual Report to Trustees: STU-Employer Life and Disability Fund, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 55/13)
    - Johnson and Higgins' Annual Report to Trustees: STU-Employer Life and Disability Fund, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 55/14)
    - Johnson and Higgins' Annual Report to Trustees: STU-Employer Life and Disability Fund, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 55/15)
    - Johnson and Higgins' Actuarial Valuation Report, 1965 (Box-folder 55/16)
    - Employer Pension Trust Fund: Financial Statements, Supplemental Schedule, 1968 (Box-folder 55/17)
    - Employer Pension Trust Fund: Financial Statements, 1967 (Box-folder 55/18)
    - Johnson and Higgins' Annual Report to Trustees: STU-Employer Life and Disability Fund, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 55/19)
    - Johnson and Higgins' Annual Report to Trustees: STU-Employer Life and Disability Fund, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 55/20)
    - Johnson and Higgins' Actuarial Valuation Report, 1968 (Box-folder 55/21)
    - Johnson and Higgins' Annual Report to Trustees: STU-Employer Life and Disability Fund, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 55/22)
    - Johnson and Higgins' Annual Report to Trustees: STU-Employer Life and Disability Fund, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 55/23)
    - Board of Trustees Meetings: STU Employer Life and Disability Fund, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 55/24)
    - STU-Employer Life and Disability Fund: Balance Sheets and Receipts, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 55/25)
    - Messages Regarding Life and Disability, Collective Bargaining, Strike, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 55/26)
    - STU-Employer Life and Disability Fund: Financial Statements and Opinion of Certified Public Accountants, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 55/27)
    - STU-Employer Life and Disability Fund: Paid Claims Reports, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 55/28)
    - STU-Employer Life and Disability Fund, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 55/29)
    - Cash, 1934-1938 (Box-folder 55/30)
    - Cash, 1938-1943 (Box-folder 55/31)
    - Cash, 1943-1950 (Box-folder 55/32)
    - Cash, 1950-1958 (Box-folder 55/33)
    - Cash, 1958-1965 (Box-folder 55/34)
    - Cash, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 55/35)
    - Cash, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 55/36)
    - Tax Forms, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 56/1)
    - Tax Forms, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 56/2)
    - Tax Forms, 1972 (Box-folder 56/3)
    - Tax Forms, 1971 (Box-folder 56/4)
    - Tax Forms, 1970 (Box-folder 56/5)
    - Tax Forms, 1969 (Box-folder 56/6)
    - Tax Forms, 1968 (Box-folder 56/7)
    - Tax Forms, 1967 (Box-folder 56/8)
    - Tax Reports, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 56/9)
    - Unemployment Social Security, 1965 (Box-folder 56/10)
    - State/Social Security/Wage/Tax reports, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 56/11)
    - State/Social Security reports, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 56/12)
    - State/Social Security reports, 1962 (Box-folder 56/13)
    - Tax Forms, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 56/14)
    - Tax Forms, 1960 (Box-folder 56/15)
    - Tax Forms, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 56/16)
    - Tax Forms, 1941-1959 (Box-folder 56/17)
    - Tax Forms, Financial Records (1 of 2), 1960-1974 (Box-folder 56/18)
    - Tax Forms; Financial Records (2 of 2), 1960-1974 (Box-folder 56/19)
    - Elections, 1959-1974 (Box-folder 56/20)
    - ITU Strike Benefits (1 of 2), 1965-1967 (Box-folder 56/21)
    - ITU Strike Benefits (2 of 2), 1965-1967 (Box-folder 56/22)
    - Strike Benefits, 1963 (Box-folder 56/23)
    - Puyallup Valley Tribune Lock Out/Strike Benefits, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 56/24)
    - Audit Reports, Invoices, Letters from Secretary-treasurer, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 56/25)
    - Budget, 1925-1974 (Box-folder 56/26)
    - Joint Strike Committee Expenses, Legal Expenses for Libel Suit, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 56/27)
    - October 1968 Monthly Letter (Box-folder 56/28)
    - Los Angeles Herald-Examiner Strike-Lockout, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 56/29)
    - Typographical Union Mutual Aid Fund, 1964-1970 (Box-folder 56/30)
    - Mutual Aid for 1965, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 56/31)
    - Mutual Aid 1964 (Box-folder 56/32)
    - Mutual Aid Year 1963, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 56/33)
    - Mutual Aid Year 1962 (Box-folder 56/34)
    - 1947 Joint Defense Program: Roots of Northwest Mutual Aid, 1947-1965 (Box-folder 56/35)
    - Typographical Mutual Aid Fund: Financial Reports, 1950-1959 (Box-folder 56/36)
    - Monthly Financial Statements, 1955-1959 (Box-folder 56/37)
    - Monthly Financial Statements, 1949-1954 (Box-folder 56/38)
    - Monthly Financial Statements, 1943-1948 (Box-folder 56/39)
    - Monthly Financial Statements, 1938-1942 (Box-folder 56/40)
    - Monthly Financial Statements, 1933-1937 (Box-folder 56/41)
    - Monthly Financial Statements, 1928-1932 (Box-folder 56/42)
    - Monthly Financial Statements, 1923-1927 (Box-folder 56/43)
    - Monthly Itemized Financial Statements, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 56/44)
    - Form 19 IRS: ITU Negotiated Pension Plan, 1972 (Box-folder 56/45)
    - Tax Exemption Form for Local 170, 1961 (Box-folder 56/46)
    - Monthly Financial Statements, 1966 (Box-folder 56/47)
    - Monthly Financial Statements, 1965 (Box-folder 56/48)
    - Monthly Financial Statements, 1964 (Box-folder 56/49)
    - Monthly Financial Statements, 1963 (Box-folder 56/50)
    - Monthly Financial Statements, 1962 (Box-folder 56/51)
    - Monthly Financial Statements, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 56/52)
    - Monthly Financial Statements, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 56/53)
    - Monthly Financial Statements, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 56/54)
    - Monthly Financial Statements, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 56/55)
    - Monthly Financial Statements, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 56/56)
    - Tacoma Typographical Union No. 170: Bargaining Agreement, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 56/57)
    - Dues Records and Communications, 1930-1966 (Box-folder 56/58)
    - Corrections of ITU Dues Reports, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 56/59)
  - SERIES IX: COMMITTEE FILES, 1920-1959 (Box-folder 57)
    - (This box is missing: Listed on legacy finding aid as 'Committee Files'), 1920-1959 (Box-folder BOX 57)
  - SERIES X: SCRAPBOOK, Undated-1959 (Box-folder 67/1)
    - Scrapbook - "Progressive steps on the Linotype and other Typecasting and Typesetting Machines and History of the Machines and History of the NEWS AND LEDGER and NEWS TRIBUNE", Undated (Box-folder 67/1 (oversized))
- RECORD GROUP D: INTERNATIONAL TYPOGRAPHICAL UNION LOCAL 142 OLYMPIA, 1890-1975 (Box-folder 58/1-60/29, 68/1)
  - SERIES I: ORGANIZATION, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 58/24)
    - Officers, Committees, Constitutions, Bylaws, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 58/24)
  - SERIES II: CORRESPONDENCE AND FINANCIAL RECORDS, 1899-1974 (Box-folder 58/1-58/23)
    - Typographical Contract and Direct Action Flyers, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 58/1)
    - Tax and Unemployment Documents (1 of 2), 1959-1974 (Box-folder 58/2)
    - Tax and Unemployment Documents (2 of 2), 1951-1974 (Box-folder 58/3)
    - Report of Financial Secretary, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 58/4)
    - Receipts and Report of Special Assistance Forms Pertaining to the Daily Olympian Strike, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 58/5)
    - Minutes and Correspondence Regarding the Daily Olympian Strike, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 58/6)
    - Ruling Machine Correspondence (1 of 2), 1958-1974 (Box-folder 58/7)
    - Ruling Machine Correspondence (2 of 2), 1959-1974 (Box-folder 58/8)
    - Court, Labor Relations, Contract Documents, 1953-1964 (Box-folder 58/9)
    - Financial Statements, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 58/10)
    - Financial Statements, 1963-1968 (Box-folder 58/11)
    - Membership Correspondence and Apprenticeship Information, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 58/12)
    - Contracts with Quick Print and the Daily Olympian, 1957 (Box-folder 58/13)
    - Underwood Correspondence, 1945-1951 (Box-folder 58/14)
    - Newspaper Publicity, 1959 (Box-folder 58/15)
    - Labor Organization Bond, 1960-1966 (Box-folder 58/16)
    - 101st Annual Convention Souvenir Book, 1959 (Box-folder 58/17)
    - Elections, 1958-1974 (Box-folder 58/18)
    - Holiday/Sick Pay Correspondence, 1963 (Box-folder 58/19)
    - Correspondence Regarding North Pacific Bank Note Company, 1965-1972 (Box-folder 58/20)
    - Department of Labor Reports, 1959-1974 (Box-folder 58/21)
    - Souvenirs, Notes, Referendums, Thank-You Notes, 1956-1974 (Box-folder 58/22)
    - General Correspondence, 1899-1974 (Box-folder 58/23)
  - SERIES III: MINUTES, 1890-1974 (Box-folder 59/1-59/8, 68/1)
    - International Typographical Union Local 99 / Local 142 Minutes, 1890-1893 (Box-folder 59/1)
    - International Typographical Union Local 99 / Local 142 Minutes, 1893-1899 (Box-folder 59/2)
    - International Typographical Union Local 99 / Local 142 Minutes, 1930-1948 (Box-folder 59/3)
    - International Typographical Union Local 99 / Local 142 Minutes, 1948-1967 (Box-folder 59/4)
    - International Typographical Union Local 99 / Local 142 Minutes, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 59/5)
    - International Typographical Union Local 99 / Local 142 Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 59/6)
    - International Typographical Union Local 99 / Local 142 Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 59/7)
    - International Typographical Union Local 99 / Local 142 Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 59/8)
    - International Typographical Union Local 99 / Local 142 Minutes, 1899-1910 (Box-folder 68/1 (oversized))
  - SERIES IV: CONTRACT NEGOTIATIONS AND RELATED MATERIALS, 1944-1975 (Box-folder 60/1-60/29)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1968-1974 (Box-folder 60/1)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1959-1967 (Box-folder 60/2)
    - Scale Committee, 1959 (Box-folder 60/3)
    - Correspondence for Olympia Typographical Union No 142, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 60/4)
    - Labor Agreements, Political Struggle, Negotiations, 1954-1959 (Box-folder 60/5)
    - Assignment Jurisdiction Disputes at Public Printer, 1956-1959 (Box-folder 60/6)
    - Contract Negotiations, 1948-1964 (Box-folder 60/7)
    - Contracts and Negotiations (1 of 3), 1967-1969 (Box-folder 60/8)
    - Contracts and Negotiations (2 of 3), 1963-1966 (Box-folder 60/9)
    - Contracts and Negotiations (3 of 3), 1959-1962 (Box-folder 60/10)
    - Apprentice Forms, 1958-1968 (Box-folder 60/11)
    - Membership emblems, 1955-1974 (Box-folder 60/12)
    - Olympia 75th Anniversary, 1965 (Box-folder 60/13)
    - Correspondence, Olympia Jurisdictional Dispute, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 60/14)
    - Contract and Jurisdiction Negotiations, Meetings with Politicians, 1951-1958 (Box-folder 60/15)
    - Democratic Committee Presentation: State Interference with Jurisdictional Dispute, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 60/16)
    - Legal Correspondence: Olympia Jurisdictional Dispute, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 60/17)
    - Washington State printing plant, 1959 (Box-folder 60/18)
    - Audit Report, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 60/19)
    - Correspondence, Receipts, News, 1957-1964 (Box-folder 60/20)
    - Receipts for Legal and Lock-Out Expenses, 1959 (Box-folder 60/21)
    - Special Assistance, 1958-1961 (Box-folder 60/22)
    - Defense and Strike Expenditures, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 60/23)
    - Mutual Aid, 1964 (Box-folder 60/24)
    - Receipts and Invoices, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 60/25)
    - Tax Form 990, 1944-1974 (Box-folder 60/26)
    - Correspondence, Newspaper Articles, State Press Dispute, 1952-1960 (Box-folder 60/27)
    - Flyers, Pamphlets, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 60/28)
    - Member Tax Returns, Donation Acknowledgement, 1960-1965 (Box-folder 60/29)
- RECORD GROUP E: INTERNATIONAL TYPOGRAPHICAL UNION LOCAL 699 BREMERTON, 1912-1976 (Box-folder 61/1-62/23)
  - SERIES I: ORGANIZATION AND ELECTION MATERIALS, 1948, 1966-1974 (Box-folder 61/1, 61/12-61/16)
    - Organizational Records, 1966-1974 (Box-folder 61/1)
    - Election Materials, 1948, 1966-1974 (Box-folder 61/12)
    - Election Materials: Ballots, 1973 (Box-folder 61/13)
    - Election Materials: Nominations, 1974 (Box-folder 61/14)
    - Election Materials: Amendments, 1974 (Box-folder 61/15)
    - Election Materials: International and Local, 1974 (Box-folder 61/16)
  - SERIES II: CORRESPONDENCE, 1955-1974 (Box-folder 61/2-61/11)
    - General Correspondence, 1955-1974 (Box-folder 61/2)
    - Newsletters, 1974 (Box-folder 61/3)
    - Mailing List, 1974 (Box-folder 61/4)
    - Meeting Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 61/5)
    - Training Materials, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 61/6)
    - California Chapters, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 61/7)
    - Washington State Conference of Typographical Unions, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 61/8)
    - Central Labor Council, 1970 (Box-folder 61/9)
    - Stereotyper's Union, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 61/10)
    - Washington State Labor Council, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 61/11)
  - SERIES III: CONTRACTS, 1962-1976 (Box-folder 61/17-61/27)
    - Contract File, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 61/17)
    - Contracts: Crampton's Stationers, 1962 (Box-folder 61/18)
    - Contracts between Bremerton Printing Co and Dickson-Fletcher Printing Co., 1962-1974 (Box-folder 61/19)
    - Contracts: Bremerton Printing Co., 1967-1974 (Box-folder 61/20)
    - Contracts: Dickson-Fletcher Printing Co., 1962-1974 (Box-folder 61/21)
    - Contracts: Seattle Newspaper Publishers, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 61/22)
    - Contracts between Tribune Publishing Co. and Tacoma Typographical Union No.190, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 61/23)
    - Contracts: Bremerton Sun (Part 1 of 4), 1972-1974 (Box-folder 61/24)
    - Contracts: Bremerton Sun (Part 2 of 4), 1964-1972 (Box-folder 61/25)
    - Contracts: Bremerton Sun (Part 3 of 4), 1964-1974 (Box-folder 61/26)
    - Contracts: Bremerton Sun (Part 4 of 4), 1964-1976 (Box-folder 61/27)
  - SERIES IV: FINANCIAL RECORDS, 1953-1974 (Box-folder 61/28-61/39)
    - Financial Records, 1965-1974 (Box-folder 61/28)
    - Financial Records: Labor Management Welfare Pension Reports, 1959-1973 (Box-folder 61/29)
    - Income Tax Returns, 1953-1974 (Box-folder 61/30)
    - Invoices, Receipts, Reimbursement Requests (Part 1 of 3), 1968-1974 (Box-folder 61/31)
    - Invoices, Receipts, Reimbursement Requests (Part 2 of 3), 1966-1974 (Box-folder 61/32)
    - Invoices, Receipts, Reimbursement Requests (Part 3 of 3), 1965-1972 (Box-folder 61/33)
    - Mortuary Benefit Documents, 1955-1974 (Box-folder 61/34)
    - Pension Fund, 1966-1974 (Box-folder 61/35)
    - Financial Logbook Pages (Part 1 of 4), 1965-1968 (Box-folder 61/36)
    - Financial Logbook Pages (Part 1 of 4), 1968-1970 (Box-folder 61/37)
    - Financial Logbook Pages (Part 1 of 4), 1970-1973 (Box-folder 61/38)
    - Financial Logbook Pages (Part 1 of 4), 1973-1974 (Box-folder 61/39)
  - SERIES IV: FINANCIAL RECORDS, 1912-1974 (Box-folder 62/1-62/14)
    - Minutes - International Typographical Union Local 99 Local 699, 1912-1936 (Box-folder 62/1)
    - Minutes - International Typographical Union Local 99 Local 699, 1936-1948 (Box-folder 62/2)
    - Minutes - International Typographical Union Local 99 Local 699, 1948-1956 (Box-folder 62/3)
    - Minutes - International Typographical Union Local 99 Local 699, 1956-1965 (Box-folder 62/4)
    - Minutes - International Typographical Union Local 99 Local 699, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 62/5)
    - Minutes - International Typographical Union Local 99 Local 699, 1966 (Box-folder 62/6)
    - Minutes - International Typographical Union Local 99 Local 699, 1967 (Box-folder 62/7)
    - Minutes - International Typographical Union Local 99 Local 699, 1968 (Box-folder 62/8)
    - Minutes - International Typographical Union Local 99 Local 699, 1969 (Box-folder 62/9)
    - Minutes - International Typographical Union Local 99 Local 699, 1970 (Box-folder 62/10)
    - Minutes - International Typographical Union Local 99 Local 699, 1971 (Box-folder 62/11)
    - Minutes - International Typographical Union Local 99 Local 699, 1972 (Box-folder 62/12)
    - Minutes - International Typographical Union Local 99 Local 699, 1973 (Box-folder 62/13)
    - Minutes - International Typographical Union Local 99 Local 699, 1974 (Box-folder 62/14)
  - SERIES V: MEMBERSHIP MATERIALS, 1912-1974 (Box-folder 62/15-62/23)
    - Financial Record Book, 1942-1948 (Box-folder 62/15)
    - Financial Record Book, 1948-1955 (Box-folder 62/16)
    - Financial Record Book, 1955-1960 (Box-folder 62/17)
    - Financial Record Book, 1935-1944 (Box-folder 62/18)
    - Financial Record Book, 1960-1965 (Box-folder 62/19)
    - Membership Register and Forms, 1953-1972 (Box-folder 62/20)
    - Traveling Cards Issued Journal, 1912-1958 (Box-folder 62/21)
    - Membership Register and Individual Ledger for Traveling Cards (Various Union Numbers), 1912-1925 (Box-folder 62/22)
    - Secretary's Monthly Itemized Report, 1960-1974 (Box-folder 62/23)